

Cubilo, Kenneth S.

PHOTOGRAPHER & STUDENT PROGRAMMER



Hi! I am a photographer/videographer. In addition to being a photographer/videographer. I am also a student programmer, new to the programming world, but eager to learn and develop my skills. With 3 years of experience in photography and a strong desire to learn more about programming. I have recently started taking programming classes and am currently enrolled at STI Calbayog in the IT (MAWD) strand I am excited to explore more in this field. My goal is to combine my photography and programming skills to create interactive and engaging experiences for my audience. I am always on the lookout for new opportunities and challenges to grow my skills and knowledge in both fields.

M

Education

2022 - 2023

STI Calbayog

Information Technology in

Mobile App and Web Development

September 2022

Jiggie Alejandrino

Wedding Portrait & Lighting

Worshop

February 21 - March 2, 2022

University of the Philippines (UP)

Department of Journalism

Philippines Election Workshop

2019 - 2021

Calbayog City National High

Professional Skills

School (CCNHS)

GRAPHIC DESIGN

PHOTOSHOP

LIGHTROOM

ILLUSTRATOR

VEGAS PRO

HTML 5

Media Arts

Contact



+63 997 078 8938

Kennethcubilo@gmial.com

6709 Sta. Margarita Burabod Sa<mark>mar,</mark> Philippines



Experience

FREELANCE PHOTOGRAPHER - (2019 - PRESENT)

PHOTOJOURNALIST - (OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT)

Photographer on Demand (PonD News Asia)



Languages

WARAY -WARAY
ENGLISH
TAGALOG

Interests

Photography Astrophotography Food Music Movies Dogs Chess Basketball Gaming Art